<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Destini</string>

    <string name ="screen_title">Choose Your Destiny</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play again</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="What_tag">What do you do?</string>

     <string name="T1_Story">Your car has blown a tire on a winding road in the middle of nowhere with no cell phone reception. You decide to hitchhike. A rusty pickup truck rumbles to a stop next to you. A man with a wide brimmed hat with soulless eyes opens the passenger door for you and asks: \"Need a ride?\". </string>
    <string name="T1_Ans1">I say yes and thank him for the help! </string>
    <string name="T1_Ans2">I half jokingly ask him if he\'s a murderer. </string>

    <string name="T2_Story">He nods slowly, seemingly unphased by my response.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans1">Think he\'s joking, laugh and climb in.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans2">Say not thanks, I know how to change a tire.</string>

    <string name="T3_Story">As you begin to drive, the stranger starts talking about his relationship with his mother. He gets angrier and angrier by the minute. He asks you to open the glovebox. Inside you find a bloody knife, two severed fingers, and a Bruce Springsteen Greatest Hits CD. He reaches for the glove box.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans1">Tell him I love Springsteen and quickly hand him the CD.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans2">Realize it\'s him or me and take the knife and stab him.</string>

    <string name="T4_End">What? Such a cop out! Did you know traffic accidents are the second leading cause of accidental death for most adult age groups?</string>

    <string name="T5_End">As you smash through the guardrail and careen towards the jagged rocks below you reflect on the dubious wisdom of stabbing someone while they are driving a car you are in.</string>

    <string name="T6_End">You bond with the murderer while crooning verses of \"Blood Brothers\". He drops you off at the next town. Before you go he asks you if you know any good places to dump bodies. You reply: \"Try the pier.\"</string>

    <string name="T6_Again">Do you want to try again?</string>

</resources>